<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Blog Saya</title>
    <link>http://fanni.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Blog Saya</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/fanni&#34;&gt;Fanni Ikhwan&lt;/a&gt; 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:05:29 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://fanni.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building Porto</title>
      <link>http://fanni.github.io/posts/building-porto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:05:29 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fanni.github.io/posts/building-porto/</guid>
      <description>This year, 2024, looks like will be a year full of re-visiting things. Start from revisit this blog, give another shot to learn skateboarding and now I also try to going back to freelancing world. I started with visiting my Upwork account, event though I did not get much from there, but I will try another shot with Upwork this year, so I logged in to my Upwork account and found out that my account was become restricted, I had to follow an instruction to verify my profile by providing some id card and also a selfie!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Re-visit Skateboarding World</title>
      <link>http://fanni.github.io/posts/revisit-sk8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 09:03:04 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fanni.github.io/posts/revisit-sk8/</guid>
      <description>4 months ago while I was scrolling videos in Youtube shorts, the video about a man who learned to play skateboarding at his late 30s or 40s suddenly popped up. It was kind of intriguing me. From the short video I came to the channel and turned out that the channel is all about how to skate in proper way. The channel name is SkateIQ, and I went through the videos on that channel, I could say it is awesome channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Blog</title>
      <link>http://fanni.github.io/posts/this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 06:08:15 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fanni.github.io/posts/this-blog/</guid>
      <description>I generated this blog using Hugo, &amp;ldquo;a static site generator written in GO&amp;rdquo; as written in Hugo&amp;rsquo;s website. There is no other reason to use Hugo, but to fulfill my curiosity about using Hugo.
Before I&amp;rsquo;m using the Github page to host my blog, I already tried to use web hosting to host my blog. My first blog was a WordPress blog (sayafanni.wordpress.com) then I rented a hosting+domain and hosted my blog there with the same name but with a web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>http://fanni.github.io/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 17:24:45 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fanni.github.io/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>If I remember correctly, my last blog posting was 4 years ago in my personal blog that&amp;rsquo;s already dead (sayafanni.web.id). Since then I&amp;rsquo;m just writing and documenting what I&amp;rsquo;ve done in a notes with a mess structure of writing or sometimes only a bunch of keywords that I forgot what it&amp;rsquo;s all about in the next day.
So, because of those reasons, I will going back to write my experiences in a proper writing format and also publish it, just in case if there are people who are facing the same problem like I did.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
